I am Haruna Sakamoto from Team Shachi.
And,
I am Shinju Yoshise of Noinari Talksar.
I am Haruna Sakamoto of Team SHACHI.
We are the two of us from yesterday,
Today, we're going to play a game to get to know each other better.
Yay!
The game we will play today is,
Gesture game.
Yay! It's easy already. Today's game is a gesture game.
Yay!
It's easy now.
Yes, it is.
Because it says I'm good at dancing.
It says I'm good at dancing,
If we couldn't answer the question, we would have to ask ourselves what we are good at,
Dancing is the most expressive form of expression with the body.
I'll say so.
Putting pressure on each other.
Once again, as many of you already know.
I'll explain the rules. The person who makes the gesture is
From Mr. Kettle over here.
Cute.
From the cute little kettle
You draw one card, and only you can see it.
The player expresses the theme using only gestures and no voice.
The person who answers will look at the gesture and guess what the theme is.
Try to get at least 6 correct answers in one minute.
That's quite a lot.
That's one correct answer every 10 seconds, right?
I see.
Ten seconds, then.
It may be difficult to get more than 6 correct unless you keep up a good tempo.
We can do it.
Yes, we can. Yes, we can.Yes. Yes, sir.
Okay, which way do you want to go first?
First,
Confidence in the one who answers. Have you ever played a live-action game with a group?
Yes, I have.
Which were you better at?
I was better at talking.
The guessing game?
Well, let's try it first.
By all means.
You go first.
I had a lot of questions to answer,
Is that so?
I think I'm good at moving.
You can start with the one you're good at first,
See how it goes.
Okay.
Then I'll pull back,
Pearl answers.
Okay.
Let's start the one-minute gesture game.
Start!
Roller coaster.
Correct!
Hairdresser.
Amazing! Easy to understand.
A cat? Correct! That's great. That's great. It's easy to understand. A cat?
Correct.
Cute.
Baseball?
Correct.
Whatever you want.
It's early.
Same.
What's that?
Not ninja, sword.Swords, not ninjas.
Lerony Kins. There.
There.
Right there.
Follow.
It's hard.
The dancers are coming in.
With sauce and cream?
Takoyaki?
Insta-glam?
Ahhh...
Eh, the last one was difficult.
But it was close.
It was the last soft ice cream parfait.
It was close.
But the tempo was pretty good.
It was great.
It was so fast.
I wonder how many were there?
At first it was just a few questions in a row, pump, pump, pump.
It was really easy to understand.
It was amazing. It was fast.
The first question was also the first one.
This is the first one.
Roller coaster.
When the climb happens, it's already a roller coaster. That's right. It's already a roller coaster because there's a lot of climbing going on.
Cute.
It was a roller coaster.
After that, Samurai also said at the end, so I guess that was OK.
That was OK.
This one, the first one.
When I did it with one hand, it looked like a baseball player,
I did it with both hands,
He answered right away.
But he didn't answer,
It was very dangerous.
What was Hal's answer?
Next, Shinji-chan gestured,Shinji then gestures,
Hal answers.
All right.
I'll do my best.
Good luck.
I'm going.
Let's start the one-minute jester game.
GO!
Onigiri
Otsuji
Otsuji?
Big appetite! Delicious!
Osaka
Takagi
Takagi Takagi
Onigiri
rice
dog
what
I wonder what it is.
Wizard
It's a great song, isn't it? Ah! Wizard! Wizard! Oh! Oh, wow! Oh! Hey, what's that?
Oh!
Singing, karaoke, uh-huh, uh-huh, what is it?
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Brushing your teeth?
Mm-hmm.
Brush?
Mmm-hmm.
Clean sweep!
What's that?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.Mmm-hmm.
What, what, what, what?
Uh-uh-uh-uh.
Mopu? Brush?
Are you peeking?
What? What is it?
Teeth? Teeth? Is he brushing his teeth?
Brushing my teeth? Toothbrush?
What? Rags and bristles?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Huh?
Wait a minute. I don't get it.
I'm sure you'll figure it out.
Wait. I want to answer. Let's extend the discussion. Let me answer this one.
Do you understand?
Do it again.
Uh, right? And what's that you're singing? Do you recognize it? I know what it is. Do it again. Here we go.
Oh, right.
What are you singing? What? Are you writing this?
That's great. That's great.
I saw that. That's great.
He's writing.
Why?
Dentist!
What's this?
Dentist.
So I guess you'll have to do it yourself.
Oh, but it's fun.
This is fun.
It's fun.
Announcement of the results
The results are in!
I made a gesture, and Shin-chan responded with 5 answers.
That's amazing.
Really amazing.
There was only one left, wasn't there?
The one I could answer,The ones I could answer,
Four.
Including the company, there were five.
That's frustrating.
It took me a little bit of time.
But it was very easy to understand.
If you look at it like you understand it, I think it's already a meeting dentist.
It was good.
That's frustrating.
It was fun.
We laughed a lot.
We got to know each other a little better.
For sure.
We worked hard.
I did my best. Thank you very much.
So tomorrow, we would like to have a bit of a serious talk with these two.
We talked about slam dunks and laughed at lecia today,
Tomorrow is a serious talk, so what kind of talk will we have coming up?
I hope you are all looking forward to it.
So, here we are so far with Haruna Sakamoto, who is wearing a team shirt,
and Chisato Kishii of Yukinari and Size.
Bye bye!
See you all again.
See you all soon.
See you soon!